Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 3, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- Box: 25, Folder: 23, Publication (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Item 1: Wage and Salary Increase, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 23)
- Box: 25, Folder: 24, Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Item 1: Shelby County Tuberculosis Society, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 24)
- Box: 25, Folder: 25, Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1954; Publication (Box 25, Folder 25)
- Box: 25, Folder: 26, Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
  - Item 1: Schedule Cuts, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 26)
- Box: 25, Folder: 27, Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
  - Item 1: Attack In Welding Department, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 27)
- Box: 25, Folder: 28, Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
  - Item 1: New Policy of Disciplinary Action, 1954; Publication (Box 25, Folder 28)
- Box: 25, Folder: 29, Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
  - Item 1: Strikes, 1954; Publication (Box 25, Folder 29)
- Box: 25, Folder: 30, Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
  - Item 1: Loss Of Work Due To Steel Shortages, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 30)
- Box: 25, Folder: 31, Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
  - Item 1: Temporary Separation Unemployment Compensation Benefits, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 31)
- Box: 25, Folder: 32, Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 32)
- Box: 25, Folder: 33, Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 33)
- Box: 25, Folder: 34, Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
  - Item 1: Production and Manpower Reduction, 1954; Publication (Box 25, Folder 34)
- Box: 25, Folder: 35, Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
  - Item 1: Health Regulations, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 35)
- Box: 25, Folder: 36, Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 36)
- Box: 25, Folder: 37, Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
  - Item 1: Wildcat Work Stoppage, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 37)
- Box: 25, Folder: 38, Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
  - Item 1: Elections and Voting, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 38)
- Box: 25, Folder: 39, Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
  - Item 1: Work Stoppage, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 39)
- Box: 25, Folder: 40, Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
  - Item 1: Shelby County Tuberculosis Society, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 40)
- Box: 25, Folder: 41, Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
  - Item 1: Protection Against Increases In Living, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 41)
- Box: 25, Folder: 42, Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
  - Item 1: Expansion of Facilities, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 42)
- Box: 25, Folder: 43, Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
  - Item 1: Salary Limitations, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 43)
- Box: 25, Folder: 44, Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
  - Item 1: Promotions, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 44)
- Box: 25, Folder: 45, Publication (Box 25, Folder 45)
  - Item 1: Returning Damaged Machines, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 45)
- Box: 25, Folder: 46, Publication (Box 25, Folder 46)
  - Item 1: Blood Donations, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 46)
- Box: 25, Folder: 47, Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
  - Item 1: Production Landmarks, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 47)
- Box: 25, Folder: 48, Publication (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 48)
- Box: 25, Folder: 49, Publication (Box 25, Folder 49)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 49)
- Box: 25, Folder: 50, Publication (Box 25, Folder 50)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 50)
- Box: 25, Folder: 51, Publication (Box 25, Folder 51)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 51)
- Box: 25, Folder: 52, Publication (Box 25, Folder 52)
  - Item 1: Expansion of Facilities, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 52)
- Box: 25, Folder: 53, Publication (Box 25, Folder 53)
  - Item 1: Walkout, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 53)
- Box: 25, Folder: 54, Publication (Box 25, Folder 54)
  - Item 1: Employee Briefing, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 54)
- Box: 25, Folder: 55, Publication (Box 25, Folder 55)
  - Item 1: Future Production And Employment Outlook, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 55)
- Box: 25, Folder: 56, Publication (Box 25, Folder 56)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 56)
- Box: 25, Folder: 57, Publication (Box 25, Folder 57)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 57)
- Box: 25, Folder: 58, Publication (Box 25, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 58)
- Box: 25, Folder: 59, Publication (Box 25, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 59)
- Box: 25, Folder: 60, Publication (Box 25, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 60)
- Box: 25, Folder: 61, Publication (Box 25, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 61)
- Box: 25, Folder: 62, Publication (Box 25, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 62)
- Box: 25, Folder: 63, Publication (Box 25, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 63)
- Box: 25, Folder: 64, Publication (Box 25, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 64)
- Box: 25, Folder: 65, Publication (Box 25, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 65)
- Box: 25, Folder: 66, Publication (Box 25, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: Shutdown For Inventory, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 66)
- Box: 25, Folder: 67, Publication (Box 25, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: Blood Donations, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 67)
- Box: 25, Folder: 68, Publication (Box 25, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: Blood Donations, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 68)
- Box: 25, Folder: 69, Publication (Box 25, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 69)
- Box: 25, Folder: 70, Publication (Box 25, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 70)
- Box: 25, Folder: 71, Publication (Box 25, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: Termination of Arbitrator, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 71)
    Author: George E Moredock Jr.
- Box: 25, Folder: 72, Publication (Box 25, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: Competition Means Progress, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 72)
    Author: Adam J. Condo
- Box: 25, Folder: 73, Publication (Box 25, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: Competition Means Progress, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 73)
- Box: 25, Folder: 74, Publication (Box 25, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Fires, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 74)
- Box: 25, Folder: 75, Publication (Box 25, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Pattern Makers League, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 75)
- Box: 25, Folder: 76, Publication (Box 25, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: Pensions, Welfare and Health Plans, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 76)
- Box: 25, Folder: 77, Publication (Box 25, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 77)
- Box: 25, Folder: 78, Publication (Box 25, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 78)
    Author: W.D. Bryson
- Box: 25, Folder: 79, Publication (Box 25, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 79)
- Box: 25, Folder: 80, Publication (Box 25, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Performance of Memphis Works, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 80)
- Box: 25, Folder: 81, Publication (Box 25, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 81)
- Box: 25, Folder: 82, Publication (Box 25, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: Change In Management, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 82)
    Author: C.N. McIntire
- Box: 25, Folder: 83, Publication (Box 25, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 83)
- Box: 25, Folder: 84, Publication (Box 25, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Negotiations Between The Union and Company, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 84)
- Box: 25, Folder: 85, Publication (Box 25, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 85)
    Author: Russell F. Denney
- Box: 25, Folder: 86, Publication (Box 25, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 86)
- Box: 25, Folder: 87, Publication (Box 25, Folder 87)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 87)
- Box: 25, Folder: 88, Publication (Box 25, Folder 88)
  - Item 1: Wildcat" Work Disturbance, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 88)
- Box: 25, Folder: 89, Publication (Box 25, Folder 89)
  - Item 1: Negotiations Between The Company and Union, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 89)
- Box: 25, Folder: 90, Publication (Box 25, Folder 90)
  - Item 1: Increase In Wages And Salaries, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 90)
- Box: 25, Folder: 91, Publication (Box 25, Folder 91)
  - Item 1: Increase In Wages And Salaries, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 91)
- Box: 25, Folder: 92, Publication (Box 25, Folder 92)
  - Item 1: Safety Both In and Out Of Work, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 92)
- Box: 25, Folder: 93, Publication (Box 25, Folder 93)
  - Item 1: Settlement Between The Company and The Union, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 93)
- Box: 25, Folder: 94, Publication (Box 25, Folder 94)
  - Item 1: Discussions Between The Company and The Union, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 94)
- Box: 25, Folder: 95, Publication (Box 25, Folder 95)
  - Item 1: Shutdown For Inventory, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 95)
- Box: 25, Folder: 96, Publication (Box 25, Folder 96)
  - Item 1: Wildcat Strike, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 96)
- Box: 25, Folder: 97, Publication (Box 25, Folder 97)
  - Item 1: Effects Of The Wildcat Work Stoppage, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 97)
- Box: 25, Folder: 98, Publication (Box 25, Folder 98)
  - Item 1: Pension, Health and Welfare Plans, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 98)
- Box: 25, Folder: 99, Publication (Box 25, Folder 99)
  - Item 1: Letter To Mr. J. Douglas Brown, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 99)
    Author: P.A. Carlstone
- Box: 25, Folder: 100, Publication (Box 25, Folder 100)
  - Item 1: Unauthorized Work Stoppage, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 100)
- Box: 25, Folder: 101, Publication (Box 25, Folder 101)
  - Item 1: News Release, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 101)
- Box: 25, Folder: 102, Publication (Box 25, Folder 102)
  - Item 1: Safety Improvement, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 102)
- Box: 25, Folder: 103, Publication (Box 25, Folder 103)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 103)
- Box: 25, Folder: 104, Publication (Box 25, Folder 104)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1955; Publication (Box 25, Folder 104)
    Author: F.A. Graflund
- Box: 25, Folder: 105, Publication (Box 25, Folder 105)
  - Item 1: Cut Backs In Manpower and Production, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 105)
- Box: 25, Folder: 106, Publication (Box 25, Folder 106)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 106)
- Box: 25, Folder: 107, Publication (Box 25, Folder 107)
  - Item 1: Delay In Cost Of Living Adjustment, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 107)
- Box: 25, Folder: 108, Publication (Box 25, Folder 108)
  - Item 1: End of Wildcat Strike, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 108)
- Box: 25, Folder: 109, Publication (Box 25, Folder 109)
  - Item 1: Unauthorized Work Stoppage, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 109)
- Box: 25, Folder: 110, Publication (Box 25, Folder 110)
  - Item 1: Abuse Of Equipment, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 110)
- Box: 25, Folder: 111, Publication (Box 25, Folder 111)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 111)
- Box: 25, Folder: 112, Publication (Box 25, Folder 112)
  - Item 1: Health-Welfare Plans, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 112)
- Box: 25, Folder: 113, Publication (Box 25, Folder 113)
  - Item 1: Negotiations With Labor Union, 1953; Publication (Box 25, Folder 113)
- Box: 25, Folder: 114, Publication (Box 25, Folder 114)
  - Item 1: Annual Community Chest Campaign, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 114)
- Box: 25, Folder: 115, Publication (Box 25, Folder 115)
  - Item 1: Letter To Plant Protection Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 115)
- Box: 25, Folder: 116, Publication (Box 25, Folder 116)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Non-Managerial Salaried Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 116)
- Box: 25, Folder: 117, Publication (Box 25, Folder 117)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 117)
- Box: 25, Folder: 118, Publication (Box 25, Folder 118)
  - Item 1: Letter To Managerial Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 118)
- Box: 25, Folder: 119, Publication (Box 25, Folder 119)
  - Item 1: Letter To Memphis Works Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 119)
- Box: 25, Folder: 120, Publication (Box 25, Folder 120)
  - Item 1: Lay-Offs, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 120)
    Author: C.W. Harter
- Box: 25, Folder: 121, Publication (Box 25, Folder 121)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 121)
- Box: 25, Folder: 122, Publication (Box 25, Folder 122)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 122)
- Box: 25, Folder: 123, Publication (Box 25, Folder 123)
  - Item 1: Letter To The Managerial Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 123)
- Box: 25, Folder: 124, Publication (Box 25, Folder 124)
  - Item 1: Letter To The Harvester People, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 124)
- Box: 25, Folder: 125, Publication (Box 25, Folder 125)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 125)
- Box: 25, Folder: 126, Publication (Box 25, Folder 126)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 126)
- Box: 25, Folder: 127, Publication (Box 25, Folder 127)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 127)
- Box: 25, Folder: 128, Publication (Box 25, Folder 128)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 128)
- Box: 25, Folder: 129, Publication (Box 25, Folder 129)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Production And Maintenance Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 129)
- Box: 25, Folder: 130, Publication (Box 25, Folder 130)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Non-Managerial Salaried Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 130)
- Box: 25, Folder: 131, Publication (Box 25, Folder 131)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 131)
- Box: 25, Folder: 132, Publication (Box 25, Folder 132)
  - Item 1: Letter To The Managerial Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 132)
- Box: 25, Folder: 133, Publication (Box 25, Folder 133)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 133)
- Box: 25, Folder: 134, Publication (Box 25, Folder 134)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Non-Managerial Salaried Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 134)
- Box: 25, Folder: 135, Publication (Box 25, Folder 135)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 135)
- Box: 25, Folder: 136, Publication (Box 25, Folder 136)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 136)
- Box: 25, Folder: 137, Publication (Box 25, Folder 137)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 137)
- Box: 25, Folder: 138, Publication (Box 25, Folder 138)
  - Item 1: Letter To The Managerial Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 138)
- Box: 25, Folder: 139, Publication (Box 25, Folder 139)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 139)
- Box: 25, Folder: 140, Publication (Box 25, Folder 140)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 140)
- Box: 25, Folder: 141, Publication (Box 25, Folder 141)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 141)
- Box: 25, Folder: 142, Publication (Box 25, Folder 142)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Employees, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 142)
- Box: 25, Folder: 143, Publication (Box 25, Folder 143)
  - Item 1: Steelworker's Strike, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 143)
- Box: 25, Folder: 144, Publication (Box 25, Folder 144)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 144)
    Author: John L. McCaffrey
- Box: 25, Folder: 145, Publication (Box 25, Folder 145)
  - Item 1: Letter To The Managerial Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 145)
- Box: 25, Folder: 146, Publication (Box 25, Folder 146)
  - Item 1: Letter To The Managerial Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 146)
- Box: 25, Folder: 147, Publication (Box 25, Folder 147)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 147)
- Box: 25, Folder: 148, Publication (Box 25, Folder 148)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 148)
- Box: 25, Folder: 149, Publication (Box 25, Folder 149)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 149)
- Box: 25, Folder: 150, Publication (Box 25, Folder 150)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 150)
- Box: 25, Folder: 151, Publication (Box 25, Folder 151)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 151)
- Box: 25, Folder: 152, Publication (Box 25, Folder 152)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 152)
- Box: 25, Folder: 153, Publication (Box 25, Folder 153)
  - Item 1: Letter To The People, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 153)
- Box: 25, Folder: 154, Publication (Box 25, Folder 154)
  - Item 1: Letter To The Managerial Organization, 1952; Publication (Box 25, Folder 154)
- Box: 25, Folder: 155, Publication (Box 25, Folder 155)
  - Item 1: Letter TO All Employees Represented By UAW-CIO, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 155)
- Box: 25, Folder: 156, Publication (Box 25, Folder 156)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 156)
- Box: 25, Folder: 157, Publication (Box 25, Folder 157)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 157)
    Author: R.C. Archer
- Box: 25, Folder: 158, Publication (Box 25, Folder 158)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 158)
- Box: 25, Folder: 159, Publication (Box 25, Folder 159)
  - Item 1: Letter TO All Employees Represented By UAW-CIO, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 159)
- Box: 25, Folder: 160, Publication (Box 25, Folder 160)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 160)
- Box: 25, Folder: 161, Publication (Box 25, Folder 161)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 161)
- Box: 25, Folder: 162, Publication (Box 25, Folder 162)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 162)
- Box: 25, Folder: 163, Publication (Box 25, Folder 163)
  - Item 1: Letter TO All Employees Represented By UAW-CIO, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 163)
- Box: 25, Folder: 164, Publication (Box 25, Folder 164)
  - Item 1: Management Reports, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 164)
- Box: 25, Folder: 165, Publication (Box 25, Folder 165)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 165)
- Box: 25, Folder: 166, Publication (Box 25, Folder 166)
  - Item 1: Letter TO All Employees Represented By UAW-CIO, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 166)
- Box: 25, Folder: 167, Publication (Box 25, Folder 167)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 167)
- Box: 25, Folder: 168, Publication (Box 25, Folder 168)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 168)
- Box: 25, Folder: 169, Publication (Box 25, Folder 169)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 169)
- Box: 25, Folder: 170, Publication (Box 25, Folder 170)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 170)
- Box: 25, Folder: 171, Publication (Box 25, Folder 171)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 171)
- Box: 25, Folder: 172, Publication (Box 25, Folder 172)
  - Item 1: Christmas Gifts, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 172)
- Box: 25, Folder: 173, Publication (Box 25, Folder 173)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 173)
- Box: 25, Folder: 174, Publication (Box 25, Folder 174)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Harvester Works People, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 174)
    Author: W.J. Reilly
- Box: 25, Folder: 175, Publication (Box 25, Folder 175)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 175)
- Box: 25, Folder: 176, Publication (Box 25, Folder 176)
  - Item 1: Letter To Memphis Works Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 176)
- Box: 25, Folder: 177, Publication (Box 25, Folder 177)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 177)
- Box: 25, Folder: 178, Publication (Box 25, Folder 178)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 178)
- Box: 25, Folder: 179, Publication (Box 25, Folder 179)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 179)
- Box: 25, Folder: 180, Publication (Box 25, Folder 180)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 180)
- Box: 25, Folder: 181, Publication (Box 25, Folder 181)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 181)
- Box: 25, Folder: 182, Publication (Box 25, Folder 182)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 182)
- Box: 25, Folder: 183, Publication (Box 25, Folder 183)
  - Item 1: Late Bulletin, Publication (Box 25, Folder 183)
- Box: 25, Folder: 184, Publication (Box 25, Folder 184)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 184)
- Box: 25, Folder: 185, Publication (Box 25, Folder 185)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 185)
- Box: 25, Folder: 186, Publication (Box 25, Folder 186)
  - Item 1: Employees' Benefit Association, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 186)
- Box: 25, Folder: 187, Publication (Box 25, Folder 187)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 187)
- Box: 25, Folder: 188, Publication (Box 25, Folder 188)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 188)
- Box: 25, Folder: 189, Publication (Box 25, Folder 189)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1950; Publication (Box 25, Folder 189)
- Box: 25, Folder: 190, Publication (Box 25, Folder 190)
  - Item 1: Letter To Memphis Works Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 190)
- Box: 25, Folder: 191, Publication (Box 25, Folder 191)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 191)
- Box: 25, Folder: 192, Publication (Box 25, Folder 192)
  - Item 1: Letter To Lee D. Conner, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 192)
- Box: 25, Folder: 193, Publication (Box 25, Folder 193)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 193)
- Box: 25, Folder: 194, Publication (Box 25, Folder 194)
  - Item 1: Letter To All Memphis Works Employees, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 194)
- Box: 25, Folder: 195, Publication (Box 25, Folder 195)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 195)
- Box: 25, Folder: 196, Publication (Box 25, Folder 196)
  - Item 1: Management Bulletin, 1951; Publication (Box 25, Folder 196)
- Box: 25, Folder: 197, Publication (Box 25, Folder 197)
  - Item 1: The Man and His Job, 1955; Publication (Box 25, Folder 197)
- Box: 25, Folder: 198, Publication (Box 25, Folder 198)
  - Item 1: Intraorganizational Bargaining In Labor Negotiations, 1966; Publication (Box 25, Folder 198)
- Box: 25, Folder: 199, Publication (Box 25, Folder 199)